

# Cian Ronayne

- Q Dublin ,Ireland
- +353862471058
- cianronaynel@gmail.com
- cian-ronayne.com

#### **SKILLS**

Adobe Photoshop

SEO Copywriting

Google Analytics

Html & CSS

Data Analysis

## Certifications



Fundamentals of Digital Marketing



Inbound Certified



Basics of SEO

## **Interests**











## HELLO,

I am a Digital Marketing Executive with experience in the creation and management of digital marketing strategies and campaigns for Ireland's largest independently owned travel company.

With experience operating multiple digital channels for a range of leading Irish travel agencies; I help build successful digital marketing strategies that increase brand awareness, promote customer engagement and drive web traffic and conversions.



#### **EDUCATION**

- National College of Ireland
   (BA (Honours) in Marketing Practice, 2nd class honors grade 1.)
- Dublin City University
   (BA in International Relations, withdrew after completing 2 out of 4 years of study.)
  - Killester College of Further Education (Information Technology, Level 5 QQI Certificate.)
- Skerries Community College
  (Achieved 390 points in the Leaving Certificate.)



## WORK EXPERIENCE

- DIGITAL MARKETING EXECUTIVE:
   Club Travel HRG Ireland, Dublin
   (Oct 2018 present)
- DATA ENTRY CLERK: Tickets.ie, Dublin (Sep 2018 - Sep 2018)
- MOVER: Two Men And A Truck, Chicago (May 2018 Aug 2018)
- FOOD & BEVERAGE ASSOCIATE: HMSHost Interantional, Dublin Airport (Jul 2015 - Jan 2016)
- RETAIL ASSISTANT: Guinness Storehouse, Dublin (May 2017 - Jun 2017)